And you're going to take your boning knife, once again, the same knife that you used to filet the fish.
You need to kind of feel; this is the really messy, dirty job.
You got to get into it.
You want to feel the pin bone and you want to go along the top as much, as close as you can to the bone without losing any flesh.
Because you don't want to throw away what you just paid good money for.
You cut both sides of the pin bone, take the pin bone out but you're trying to cut right along the edge.
You're losing very little flesh and there are bones, rows of bones, probably eight or ten bones in that piece of meat right there.
Okay, we're going to take the pin bones out of this filet as well.
Once again, you're feeling with your fingertips along, to find the row.
You don't want to go any further than the last bone.
And you want to cut right along the edge of the bones, the best you can, without losing any yield, wasting any flesh.
And, I'm going to trim this side out as well.
And there's your pin bone right there.
And that's edible, if you want to pick through the bones or, if not, you've got a boneless filet.